freeplays.com 2009-06-26

# Privacy policy - FreePlays.com

**_FreePlays.com (the "Site") is committed to safeguarding your privacy on-line. Please read this privacy statement to understand how any personal information you give us will be treated as you make full use of our Site. This policy and statement may change from time to time, so please check back periodically._**

By visiting the Site, you give us certain non-personal information without knowing it. This information includes your domain, IP address, browser type, operating system, what sites you’ve visited and where you move in our Site. This is done automatically when you visit almost any site. We use this information in order to help make our site more useful for you. Other features of our site require you to create user names and/or an _account_. While we do not ask you to directly register with our site, you will need such information in order to access these specific features.

At this time, we do not keep demographical statistics. If a time comes when we do request any personally-identifying information from you, we will modify this statement accordingly.

FreePlays.com currently uses cookies to maintain state accross our site and to provide you with the best user experience possible. We do not store unencryped personal information within cookies, nor do we make any attempt to install third-party cookies intended for malicious or monitoring purposes. 

We have a strict opt-in email policy and do not send any unsolicited emails from freeplays.com. If you are receiving emails from freeplays.com, it means you have signed up on freeplays.com or one of our affiliate sites. You may cancel these emails at any time by clicking the "remove email" link in one of our emails, or simply click here to remove your email address. If you have any comments or questions about this privacy statement, you may send them to [support@sports-spectrum.com](mailto:support@sports-spectrum.com).

**Please help support FreePlays.com and our site services.  
**
